<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DataFest 2020 @ EDI on DataFest @ EDI</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DataFest 2020 @ EDI on DataFest @ EDI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/coc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/coc/</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at University of Edinburgh is committed to providing a welcoming and harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), or technology choices. We do not tolerate harassment of event participants in any form. Sexual language and imagery is not appropriate for any event venue, including talks, workshops, social activities, social media, and other online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>How do I sign up? Click here to sign up. Please fill out the form fully. You can sign up as a 4-5 (gets priority) or 2-3 person team or leave us your information to be matched with others looking for teams. Seats are limited, so register early! The registration deadline is Friday, 21 February, at 17:00.
 Is there a registration fee? No, there is no registration fee. However note that the event takes significant resources to run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/media/</guid>
      <description>If you would like to write about or cover ASA DataFestTM in any way, please don&#39;t hesitate to contact us.
 DataFest Shows Spike in Growth, Provides Immersive Experience - AMSTAT News, September 1, 2017
 Edmunds.com sponsors data set for fifth ASA DataFest at UCLA - Daily Bruin - April 27, 2015
 DataFest draws hundreds to solve stats challenges - The Chronicle - 23 March 2015
 A Festival of Data: Student Perspectives - AMSTAT News, 1 September 2014</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/schedule/</guid>
      <description>All events take place @ Bayes Centre
Friday, 13 March 2020 Welcome!
 4-6pm - Registration 6-7pm - Kickoff &amp;amp; Meet the data - G.03 7pm - Dinner  Consultants available for help until midnight, you can work as late as you like.
Saturday, 14 March 2020 Carry on!
 9am - Breakfast 12:30pm - Lunch 5:30pm - Group photo 6:00pm - Dinner 11:50pm - Midnight snack  Consultants available for help until midnight, you can work as late as you like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign up</title>
      <link>/signup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/signup/</guid>
      <description>Click on the option that applies to you. Regardless of the option you choose, you will automatically be placed on the ASA DataFestTM mailing list to receive updates and announcements.
Registration deadline is 17:00 on Friday, 21 Feb 2020.
Seats are limited, sign up before it&#39;s too late!
Participants Option 1: Team sign-up (4-5 students)  Click here to sign up as a team of 4 to 5 students. Students signing up in this category will be given priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at University of Edinburgh cannot run without your support!
In you are interested in sponsoring this event, click here for more information.
Please contact us if you are interested in sponsorship and/or have any questions.
Sponsors The School of Mathematics at The University of Edinburgh is situated in the James Clerk Maxwell Building within the King&#39;s Buildings campus, 4 km south of Edinburgh city centre. There are over 50 academic and related staff and around 60 research students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsorship</title>
      <link>/sponsorship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsorship/</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at University of Edinburgh cannot run without your support!
Please contact us if you are interested in sponsorship and/or have any questions.
Impact of Your Sponsorship Your sponsorship of ASA DataFestTM benefits the ASA DataFestTM @ University of Edinburgh. Any residual funds will support undergraduate statistics education, foster the new generation of data science, and advance our mission of promoting the use of data in the understanding of our environment, our social relationships, and our physical and virtual selves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshops/</guid>
      <description>We are planning on hosting a series of workshops leading up to the event to help participants prepare for the event.
Let us know if you&#39;re interested in running / hosting a pre-DataFest workshop!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>