<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DataFest 2024 @ EDI on DataFest-2024</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DataFest 2024 @ EDI on DataFest-2024</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/coc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/coc/</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at University of Edinburgh is committed to providing a welcoming and harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), or technology choices. We do not tolerate harassment of event participants in any form. Sexual language and imagery is not appropriate for any event venue, including talks, workshops, social activities, social media, and other online media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataFest 2020</title>
      <link>/df2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/df2020/</guid>
      <description>Eight teams participated in the DataFest @ EDI 2020 - COVID-19 Virtual Data Challenge over two weeks between 30 May and 13 June, 2020.&#xA;For this competition, we challenged participants to explore the societal impacts of the COVID-19 pandemic other than its direct health outcomes. Participants were allowed to explore everything from the effects on pollution levels, transportation levels, or working from home. They could investigate changes in the number of people posting on TikTok with their families or do an analysis on online education.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataFest 2024 Sponsors</title>
      <link>/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFest at University of Edinburgh cannot run without your support!&#xA;We need lots of consultant hours so we hope that you&amp;rsquo;ll consider supporting us with your time this year! Click here as a consultant.&#xA;To find out more about how you can support DataFest at University of Edinburgh, and don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to contact us with sponsorship questions.&#xA;Huge thanks to our sponsors, and we&amp;rsquo;re hoping to add more to this list!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>How do I sign up? Go to the Sign Up tab to register. Please fill out the form fully.&#xA;You can sign up as a 4-5 (gets priority) or 2-3 person team or leave us your information to be matched with others looking for teams. Seats are limited, so register early! The registration deadline is 11th March, at 17:00.&#xA;Is there a registration fee? No, there is no registration fee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Past DataFests</title>
      <link>/df2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/df2021/</guid>
      <description>Data Fest 2021 Ediburgh Thirty-six teams participated in the ASA DataFest @ EDI 2021 between 26-28 March 2021.&#xA;ASA DataFest is a data analysis competition where teams of up to five students attack a large and complex surprise dataset over a weekend to find and communicate insights into the data. The teams that impress the judges win prizes, and the event is a great opportunity for them to gain some data analyses work experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practicals</title>
      <link>/practicals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/practicals/</guid>
      <description>How do I enter the venue? The Nucleus Building is a new shared learning, teaching and social hub at the heart of The King’s Buildings campus. See the location from the Google map&#xA;After normal working hours, access to the venue is only possible by card. If you are not a staff or student from the University of Edinburgh and want to enter the building at these hours, please make sure that you have a phone number from someone who can open the door for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description>Technology resources Software RStudio Cloud: https://rstudio.cloud/&#xA;EDINA (https://noteable.edina.ac.uk/launch) for access to R and Python&#xA;Python via different platforms; Google Colab, Jupyter notebook or you can install local platforms such as Anaconda.&#xA;Code repository, version control, and collaboration GitHub: https://www.github.com&#xA;GitLab: https://about.gitlab.com&#xA;Happy Git with R: https://happygitwithr.com/&#xA;For the installation of related tools, you can follow the instructions available for R and RStudio for Github.&#xA;Interactive visualisations and dashboards Shiny:&#xA;All things Shiny: https://shiny.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/schedule/</guid>
      <description>All events take place on-site. We&amp;rsquo;ll use MS Teams for communication.&#xA;Event details When: Friday, March 22 at 6:00 pm - Sunday, March 24 at 7 pm&#xA;Where: Hawthorn Teaching Room, Nucleus Building, The King&amp;rsquo;s Buildings campus, The University of Edinburgh, EH9 3FG&#xA;Friday, 22 March 2024 Welcome!&#xA;📣 5-6pm - Registration&#xA;📣 6-6:30pm - Welcome; Overview of the event; Introducing the dataset&#xA;💻 6:30-7pm - Setting up your team</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign up</title>
      <link>/signup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/signup/</guid>
      <description>Seats are limited, sign up before it&amp;rsquo;s too late! Deadline is 11 March 2024, 5pm UK time.&#xA;Participants Option 1: Team sign-up (2-5 students) Click here to sign up as a team of 2 to 5 students. Students signing up in this category will be given priority.&#xA;Option 2: Looking for teammates If you do not have a team in mind but you&amp;rsquo;re looking for teammates, click here to leave us your information so that you can be matched with others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support DataFest</title>
      <link>/sponsorship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sponsorship/</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at University of Edinburgh cannot run without your support!&#xA;There are three ways you can support ASA DataFestTM as either an individual or a business:&#xA;Please consider visiting as a Visiting Consultant. Spend an hour or two getting to know the students and offering your sage advice. This is an excellent recruiting opportunity; you get to watch students working in teams, under pressure, striving to understand possibly the most complex data set they have encountered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/workshops/</guid>
      <description>We are planning on hosting a series of workshops leading up to the event to help participants prepare for the event.&#xA;Let us know if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in running / hosting a pre-DataFest workshop!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
