<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DataFest 2021 @ EDI on DataFest @ EDI</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DataFest 2021 @ EDI on DataFest @ EDI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/coc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/coc/</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at University of Edinburgh is committed to providing a welcoming and harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), or technology choices. We do not tolerate harassment of event participants in any form. Sexual language and imagery is not appropriate for any event venue, including talks, workshops, social activities, social media, and other online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DataFest 2020</title>
      <link>/df2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/df2020/</guid>
      <description>Eight teams participated in the DataFest @ EDI 2020 - COVID-19 Virtual Data Challenge over two weeks between 30 May and 13 June, 2020.
For this competition, we challenged participants to explore the societal impacts of the COVID-19 pandemic other than its direct health outcomes. Participants were allowed to explore everything from the effects on pollution levels, transportation levels, or working from home. They could investigate changes in the number of people posting on TikTok with their families or do an analysis on online education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DataFest 2021 Sponsors</title>
      <link>/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at University of Edinburgh cannot run without your support! Since we&#39;re running the event virtually this year our financial costs will be low but we need lots of mentor hours so we hope that you&#39;ll consider supporting us with your time this year! Click here as a mentor.
Click here to find out more about how you can support DataFest at University of Edinburgh, and don&#39;t hesitate to contact us with sponsorship questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>How do I sign up? Click here to sign up. Please fill out the form fully. You can sign up as a 4-5 (gets priority) or 2-3 person team or leave us your information to be matched with others looking for teams. Seats are limited, so register early! The registration deadline is Friday, 19 March, at 17:00.
 Is there a registration fee? No, there is no registration fee. However note that the event takes significant resources to run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description>Technology resources Software  RStudio Cloud: https://rstudio.cloud/
 EDINA (Link TBA) for access to R and Python
  Code repository, version control, and collaboration  GitHub: https://www.github.com
 GitLab: https://about.gitlab.com
 Happy Git with R: https://happygitwithr.com/
  Interctive visualisations and dashboards  Shiny:
 All things Shiny: https://shiny.rstudio.com/ (including a sample COVID-19 dashboard) Deploy Shiny app on shinyapps.io: https://docs.rstudio.com/shinyapps.io/getting-started.html Shiny tutorial (video): https://shiny.rstudio.com/tutorial/ Shiny tutorial (slides): https://rstudio-education.github.io/shiny-jsm18/  Tableau:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/schedule/</guid>
      <description>All events take place @ Bayes Centre
Friday, 26 March 2020 Welcome!
 6-7pm - Kickoff &amp;amp; Meet the data - Zoom  Consultants available for help until midnight, you can work as late as you like.
Saturday, 27 March 2020 Carry on!
Morning, afternoon, and evening virtual get togethers on GatherTown
Consultants available for help until midnight, you can work as late as you like.
Sunday, 15 March 2020 Wrap up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign up</title>
      <link>/signup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/signup/</guid>
      <description>Sign up forms will be available shortly!
 --  Click [here](https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=sAafLmkWiUWHiRCgaTTcYRiRHjHRDWhOuLE_6JyNA0dUMTZVUjVBR0sySDZKR0VORjVFSFVXMFRNSS4u) to sign up as a team of 4 to 5 students. Students signing up in this category will be given priority. ### Option 2: Team sign-up (2-3 students)  Click [here](https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=sAafLmkWiUWHiRCgaTTcYRiRHjHRDWhOuLE_6JyNA0dUQTlVUlRGQU43NjIxWEwxMVVETTZLWlpLWS4u) to sign up as a team of 2 to 3 students. Students signing up in this category will be added to the roster if there are seats open as of Fridsy, 21 Feb, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support DataFest</title>
      <link>/sponsorship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsorship/</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at University of Edinburgh cannot run without your support!
There are three ways you can support ASA DataFestTM as either an individual or a business:
 Please consider visiting as a Visiting Consultant. Spend an hour or two getting to know the students and offering your sage advice. This is an excellent recruiting opportunity; you get to watch students working in teams, under pressure, striving to understand possibly the most complex data set they have encountered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshops/</guid>
      <description>We are planning on hosting a series of workshops leading up to the event to help participants prepare for the event.
Let us know if you&#39;re interested in running / hosting a pre-DataFest workshop!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>