<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DataFest 2020 @ EDI on DataFest @ EDI</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DataFest 2020 @ EDI on DataFest @ EDI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>What is DataFest? ASA DataFestTM is a data analysis competition where teams of up to five students attack a large, complex, and surprise dataset over a weekend. Your job is to represent your school by finding and communicating insights into these data. The teams that impress the judges will win prizes as well as glory for their school. Everyone will have a great experience, lots of food, and fun!
ASA DataFestTM is also a great opportunity to gain experience that employers are looking for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/coc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/coc/</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at University of Edinburgh is committed to providing a welcoming and harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), or technology choices. We do not tolerate harassment of event participants in any form. Sexual language and imagery is not appropriate for any event venue, including talks, workshops, social activities, social media, and other online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competition Details</title>
      <link>/details/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/details/</guid>
      <description>When is the competition? The competition is May 30 through June 13. All projects must be submitted by June 13, 2020 at 11:59pm BST.

Who is eligible to participate? The competition is open to all undergraduate students at University of Edinburgh.

How large are the teams? Teams can be made up of 2 to 5 students.

Do I have to compete in a team? DataFest is a collaborative competition, so we strongly encourage you to work in a team to honor the spirit of the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DataFest 2020 Sponsors</title>
      <link>/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at University of Edinburgh cannot run without your support! Click here to find out more about how you can support DataFest at University of Edinburgh, and don&#39;t hesitate to contact us with sponsorship questions.
Huge thanks to our sponsors, and we&#39;re hoping to add more to this list!
Support DataFest 2020

Cauchy Sponsor 
The School of Mathematics at The University of Edinburgh is situated in the James Clerk Maxwell Building within the King&#39;s Buildings campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>How do I sign up? Click here to sign up. Please fill out the form fully. You can sign up as a 4-5 (gets priority) or 2-3 person team or leave us your information to be matched with others looking for teams. Seats are limited, so register early! The registration deadline is Friday, 21 February, at 17:00.
 Is there a registration fee? No, there is no registration fee. However note that the event takes significant resources to run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/media/</guid>
      <description>If you would like to write about or cover ASA DataFestTM in any way, please don&#39;t hesitate to contact us.
 DataFest Shows Spike in Growth, Provides Immersive Experience - AMSTAT News, September 1, 2017
 Edmunds.com sponsors data set for fifth ASA DataFest at UCLA - Daily Bruin - April 27, 2015
 DataFest draws hundreds to solve stats challenges - The Chronicle - 23 March 2015
 A Festival of Data: Student Perspectives - AMSTAT News, 1 September 2014</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description>Technology resources Software  RStudio Cloud: https://rstudio.cloud/
 EDINA (Link TBA) for access to R and Python
  Code repository, version control, and collaboration  GitHub: https://www.github.com
 GitLab: https://about.gitlab.com
 Happy Git with R: https://happygitwithr.com/
  Interctive visualisations and dashboards  Shiny:
 All things Shiny: https://shiny.rstudio.com/ (including a sample COVID-19 dashboard) Deploy Shiny app on shinyapps.io: https://docs.rstudio.com/shinyapps.io/getting-started.html Shiny tutorial (video): https://shiny.rstudio.com/tutorial/ Shiny tutorial (slides): https://rstudio-education.github.io/shiny-jsm18/  Tableau:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/schedule/</guid>
      <description>All events take place @ Bayes Centre
Friday, 13 March 2020 Welcome!
 4-6pm - Registration 6-7pm - Kickoff &amp;amp; Meet the data - G.03 7pm - Dinner  Consultants available for help until midnight, you can work as late as you like.
Saturday, 14 March 2020 Carry on!
 9am - Breakfast 12:30pm - Lunch 5:30pm - Group photo 6:00pm - Dinner 11:50pm - Midnight snack  Consultants available for help until midnight, you can work as late as you like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign up</title>
      <link>/signup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/signup/</guid>
      <description>Registration deadline Saturday, May 30 at 11:59pm BST.

  Click [here](https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=sAafLmkWiUWHiRCgaTTcYRiRHjHRDWhOuLE_6JyNA0dUMTZVUjVBR0sySDZKR0VORjVFSFVXMFRNSS4u) to sign up as a team of 4 to 5 students. Students signing up in this category will be given priority. ### Option 2: Team sign-up (2-3 students)  Click [here](https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=sAafLmkWiUWHiRCgaTTcYRiRHjHRDWhOuLE_6JyNA0dUQTlVUlRGQU43NjIxWEwxMVVETTZLWlpLWS4u) to sign up as a team of 2 to 3 students. Students signing up in this category will be added to the roster if there are seats open as of Fridsy, 21 Feb, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support DataFest</title>
      <link>/sponsorship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsorship/</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at University of Edinburgh cannot run without your support!
There are three ways you can support ASA DataFestTM as either an individual or a business:
 Please consider visiting as a Visiting Consultant. Spend an hour or two getting to know the students and offering your sage advice. This is an excellent recruiting opportunity; you get to watch students working in teams, under pressure, striving to understand possibly the most complex data set they have encountered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshops/</guid>
      <description>We are planning on hosting a series of workshops leading up to the event to help participants prepare for the event.
Let us know if you&#39;re interested in running / hosting a pre-DataFest workshop!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>